how's he doing
George Bush well he's alive but that's
about it so he's still not talking huh
my his persistent you would think after
six months of custom beatings and
torture he would talk by now
rise and shine Spartacus
now are you going to tell us what we
want to hear today why are we going to
have to resort to some darker measures
and to getting you to talk
it'll do Tim and Tim a very you don't
even know what you want with me
I'll advise you now it would be wise for
you Natalie Thomas today we are really
on the edge at yo can supervise fish in
Italian so get Bertini ah smooches
you're licking
you little us we'll be next if you
don't watch your mouth white boy
why that smug look off your face before
I wipe it off for George that's enough
Goddamn it that's enough you're going to
kill it good let me kill him he's
getting on my last nerve he's really
tickled me ass George calm down
let me take over from here I'll go get
the laptop laptop yes
flat top we've uncovered some info that
we believe will get you to tell us what
we want to hear what we want to hear
about the prophecy the prophecy
you don't want us to know anything about
what video we'll call it we've been
doing research day and night and
discovered something interesting
something astonishing please take a look
at this Chambers MO two three four five
YouTube page
yeah each solution it what that you see
over the past four years Tamers12345 one two
three four five himself has been
dropping hints about the process he
there is going to be a huge war in the
future and he's getting ready you can't
find these and she left him videos he
made in the past starting all the way
back in the year 2013 it's quite
incredible if you ask me he's planned
this first back in September 13th of
2013 we have the lazy Underground
opening video that was the first time
the prophecy was mentioned and it was by
you of all people Sportacus you told
tonic and Bartleby of a prophecy that
said the two of them would fight in a
great war
then just a month later on October 1st
2013 we get another clue
in the video Darth Vader fights Luke in
the name of su Luke a division that told
of the same war
then one year later on March 16 2014 the
prophecy was brought up again by you
Spartacus and the tamer is one two three
four five birthday bash video
you can be seen speaking without b1
Konami someone who also seems to know
about the prophecy
then jumping ahead to August 26 2016
we got mentioned of the prophecy again
in the Manic acts Mindy amv would matter
Mindi's dad claims to have a dream with
his daughter Mindy dies in a Great War
there is no doubt in my mind that he had
a dream about the prophecy it's
incredible isn't it chambers one two
three four five has been planning
something for nearly five years and
despite his YouTube channel being so
popular not a single person ever
picked up on it being able to keep all
this hidden chambers one two three four
five truly as an amazing man
I agree
megarace dosimeter cientos cuarenta
cinco y s-- animus in man boo do
Troy sunny Condell grown fans Preta ma
eres a DOS a mil press en toes cuarenta
cinco farm no habitants ojos de novo
tell becauseö not ro a Sonic undergrown
falsely Cuse
shut up
you think we're not through Sonic
Underground fans you you in
the ass
we love s you if you're really love is
ooh we are you doing tease even if it'll
be a walk the Prophet or puis je yo
Domingo wit that in all Asia that is
none of your business
we're asking the questions here so now
that you know that we know the prophecy
will you tell us what we want to hear
there's no use in lying to us anymore
mine will only resort in more pain it E
is a jingle alright then if that's
how you be then so be it
let's see if you can't still hold your
tongue after six more months of custom
torture I believe help you George Bush
make sure he suffers greatly